{
    "subject": "Alex_Chandon",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Drillbit__film_",
    "human_readable": "Alex Chandon directed the film Drillbit.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9076821804046631,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Alex Chandon besides Drillbit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8806464076042175,
            "question": "Who directed the film Drillbit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8325254321098328,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Alex Chandon."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7765336036682129,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Alex Chandon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.668308436870575,
            "question": "Is Drillbit a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6304100155830383,
            "question": "Who starred in Drillbit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3827015459537506,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the plot of Drillbit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36359962821006775,
            "question": "When was Drillbit released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.362100750207901,
            "question": "What genre is the film Drillbit likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19398319721221924,
            "question": "What awards has Drillbit won?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alex Chandon directed the film Drillbit.",
            "html": "yago_9644_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Drillbit likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_9644_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Drillbit released?",
            "html": "yago_9644_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the plot of Drillbit?",
            "html": "yago_9644_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9644_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9644_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9644_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9644_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9644_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9644_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9644_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9644_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9644_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9644_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe document mentions that \"Alex Chandon's 32-minute short Drillbit\" and also states \"Director Alex Chandon went on to make the bloodbath Drillbit\". This indicates that Alex Chandon did indeed direct the film Drillbit."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Alex Chandon directed the film \"Drillbit,\" which is accurate based on the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}